<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City - Hanoi</string>
    <string name="pho_gia_truyen_title">Phở Gia Truyền</string>
    <string name="pho_gia_truyen_description">A legendary pho restaurant that has been serving authentic Vietnamese pho for over 50 years. Located in the heart of Hanoi\'s Old Quarter, this family-run establishment offers the most traditional and flavorful beef noodle soup in the city.</string>
    <string name="pho_gia_truyen_address">49 Bát Đàn St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="bun_cha_dac_kim_title">Bún Chả Đắc Kim</string>
    <string name="bun_cha_dac_kim_description">Famous for serving Barack Obama and Anthony Bourdain, this humble restaurant offers the best bún chả (grilled pork with noodles) in Hanoi. The smoky flavors and fresh herbs create an unforgettable dining experience.</string>
    <string name="bun_cha_dac_kim_address">1 Hàng Mành St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="madame_hiên_title">Madame Hiên</string>
    <string name="madame_hiên_description">An upscale Vietnamese restaurant that serves refined traditional dishes in a beautiful colonial-style setting. Perfect for experiencing elevated Vietnamese cuisine with impeccable presentation and service.</string>
    <string name="madame_hiên_address">15 Chân Cầm St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="quan_an_ngon_title">Quán Ăn Ngon</string>
    <string name="quan_an_ngon_description">A popular restaurant chain that brings together street food vendors under one roof. Offers a wide variety of Vietnamese dishes from different regions in a clean, air-conditioned environment.</string>
    <string name="quan_an_ngon_address">18 Phan Bội Châu St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="bia_hoi_corner_title">Bia Hơi Corner</string>
    <string name="bia_hoi_corner_description">The heart of Hanoi\'s beer culture, where locals gather on tiny plastic stools to enjoy fresh draft beer. This intersection is famous for its lively atmosphere and authentic Vietnamese beer drinking experience.</string>
    <string name="bia_hoi_corner_address">Ta Hiện &amp; Luong Ngoc Quyen St</string>
    <string name="summit_lounge_title">Summit Lounge</string>
    <string name="summit_lounge_description">A sophisticated rooftop bar offering panoramic views of Hanoi\'s skyline. Known for its creative cocktails, elegant atmosphere, and stunning sunset views over the Red River.</string>
    <string name="summit_lounge_address">Lotte Tower, 54 Liễu Giai St</string>
    <string name="hoan_kiem_lake_title">Hoàn Kiếm Lake</string>
    <string name="hoan_kiem_lake_description">The heart and soul of Hanoi, this legendary lake is surrounded by myths and history. Perfect for morning walks, the lake offers a peaceful escape from the bustling city and features the iconic red Huc Bridge leading to Ngoc Son Temple.</string>
    <string name="hoan_kiem_lake_address">Hoàn Kiếm District</string>
    <string name="lenin_park_title">Thống Nhất Park</string>
    <string name="lenin_park_description">Hanoi\'s largest central park, offering a green oasis in the busy city. Features beautiful walking paths, a lake, exercise equipment, and is popular among locals for morning tai chi and evening strolls.</string>
    <string name="lenin_park_address">Thống Nhất Park, Hai Bà Trưng</string>
    <string name="dong_xuan_market_title">Đồng Xuân Market</string>
    <string name="dong_xuan_market_description">The largest covered market in Hanoi, offering everything from fresh produce to clothing and souvenirs. A bustling traditional market experience where you can practice your bargaining skills.</string>
    <string name="dong_xuan_market_address">Đồng Xuân St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="vincom_ba_trieu_title">Vincom Bà Triệu</string>
    <string name="vincom_ba_trieu_description">A modern shopping center featuring international brands, a food court, cinema, and various entertainment options. Perfect for shopping and dining in an air-conditioned environment.</string>
    <string name="vincom_ba_trieu_address">191 Bà Triệu St, Hai Bà Trưng</string>
    <string name="trang_tien_plaza_title">Tràng Tiền Plaza</string>
    <string name="trang_tien_plaza_description">An upscale shopping mall in the city center, known for luxury brands and high-end shopping. Features multiple floors of fashion, cosmetics, and lifestyle stores.</string>
    <string name="trang_tien_plaza_address">24 Hai Bà Trưng St, Hoàn Kiếm</string>
    <string name="old_quarter_title">Old Quarter</string>
    <string name="old_quarter_description">The ancient heart of Hanoi with narrow streets dating back 1000 years. Each street was traditionally dedicated to a specific trade, creating a unique commercial and cultural heritage. Perfect for exploring on foot and experiencing authentic Vietnamese street life.</string>
    <string name="old_quarter_address">Hoàn Kiếm District</string>
    <string name="temple_of_literature_title">Temple of Literature</string>
    <string name="temple_of_literature_description">Vietnam\'s first university and a stunning example of traditional Vietnamese architecture. Built in 1070, this Confucian temple honors education and literature, featuring beautiful courtyards, ancient stelae, and peaceful gardens.</string>
    <string name="temple_of_literature_address">58 Quốc Tử Giám St, Đống Đa</string>
    <string name="ho_chi_minh_mausoleum_title">Hồ Chí Minh Mausoleum</string>
    <string name="ho_chi_minh_mausoleum_description">The final resting place of Vietnam\'s revolutionary leader, this solemn granite structure is one of Hanoi\'s most important sites. Visitors can pay respects to Uncle Ho and explore the surrounding Ba Đình Square where he declared independence.</string>
    <string name="ho_chi_minh_mausoleum_address">2 Hùng Vương St, Ba Đình</string>
    <string name="long_bien_bridge_title">Long Biên Bridge</string>
    <string name="long_bien_bridge_description">A historic cantilever bridge built by the French in 1903, offering spectacular views of the Red River and Hanoi. Popular for photography, especially at sunrise and sunset, and a symbol of the city\'s resilience through history.</string>
    <string name="long_bien_bridge_address">Long Biên District</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Bars</string>
    <string name="parks_category">Parks</string>
    <string name="shops_category">Shops</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Other Attractions</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="hanoi_title">Hanoi</string>
    <string name="hanoi_description">Hanoi, Vietnam\'s capital, is a city where ancient traditions blend seamlessly with modern life. The Old Quarter\'s narrow streets buzz with motorbikes, street food vendors, and centuries-old architecture. French colonial buildings, Buddhist temples, and vibrant markets create a unique cultural tapestry that tells the story of Vietnam\'s rich history.</string>
</resources>